mynokiablog.com 2016-12-18

# Privacy Policy – My Nokia Blog

**MyNokiaBlog.com respects your privacy.**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at jay@mynokiablog.com.

At _MyNokiaBlog.com_ , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by mynokiablog.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

****  
Like many other Web sites, _MyNokiaBlog.com_ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

A “cookie” is “used for an origin website to send state information to a user’s browser and for the browser to return the state information to the origin site.”

This is used at _MyNokiaBlog.com_ to recognise when you visit, perhaps to remember settings, information, read articles, polls and commenter details.

Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and _MyNokiaBlog.com_  does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.  
**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  *  Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on mynokiablog.com.
  *  Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to mynokiablog.com and other sites on the Internet.
  *  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

  * Google Adsense
  * Carat

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on _MyNokiaBlog.com_ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

_MyNokiaBlog.com_ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. mynokiablog.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of _  MyNokiaBlog.com. _

### _MyNokiaBlog.com_  is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Take Care when using the internet.**

  * __MyNokiaBlog.com  __will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on  _ _MyNokiaBlog.com.  __
  * MyNokiaBlog.com will never ask for passwords in email. Only authorised authors/admin will see login pages requesting their password to deliver content to MyNokiaBlog.com’s readers.  _ _  
__
  *   * Please take care when following external links provided by MyNokiaBlog.com directly in posts or within comments. These links are most often directing to the news sources, and whilst we do try our best here at   _ _MyNokiaBlog.com  __to remove spam comments, there may be an occasion that one may slip through to a site we do not condone.
  * While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to  _MyNokiaBlog.com_  and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information
  * In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through  _MyNokiaBlog.com_  have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.
